brainmass.com 2011-04-27

# Privacy Policy - Homework Help from BrainMass

**BrainMass Privacy Policy**

Welcome to BrainMass.com (the " **Site** " hereafter). This document explains the policies that BrainMass (" **BM** ", " **we** ", " **us** ", or " **our** " hereafter) has instituted for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information (the "Privacy Policy" hereafter).

This Privacy Policy forms part of, and should be read in conjunction with, our Legal Terms and Conditions, found at <http://www.brainmass.com/content/terms_conditions.php>. 

BM believes that privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of Internet commerce. Our status as an Online Solution Service provider requires us to have a stringent policy regarding all of the information that we collect.

Your use of this site or BM's services constitutes acceptance of these terms and conditions. If you do not agree with these policies, please cease using this site immediately.

BM takes reasonable precautions to ensure your privacy on the terms contained in this policy. BM uses reasonable efforts to, but cannot totally prevent, unintended disclosures by such means as hackers and other unauthorized individuals, and inadvertent or illicit employee actions.

**What the Privacy Policy Covers**

Privacy Information covers BM's treatment of nonpublic personal information that we collect in connection with providing you with BrainMass.com services (such as BrainMass.com Online Teaching Assistant or User Accounts and access thereto, BrainMass.com Post-a-Problem, BrainMass.com Submit-an-Essay, BrainMass.com Solution Library and BrainMass.com Advertising Services).

If you are a former user of a BM service, we will continue to treat the nonpublic personal information we collected from you in connection with our services as described here.

We use information collected from the Online Teaching Assistant to send the Online Teaching Assistant information about BrainMass.com, to contact the Online Teaching Assistant for various reasons, and for internal accounting and other procedures. Information is used to check the Online Teaching Assistant's eligibility and to obtain and verify qualifications in regard to the application, and to support the ongoing provision of service. It is also used for login validation purposes.

We use information collected from the user, to send the user information regarding the service requested and to support the on-going provision of service.

**Information Automatically Collected**

BM may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to non-affiliated third parties as permitted by law, such as when:

  * We have your consent to share the information;
  * We need to share the information to provide the product or service you have requested;
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process.

Except for the above parties, and for use by BM's consultants and professional advisers on BM's behalf for the uses disclosed herein, BM does not share personal information with any other third parties but over time we may send you third party email offers. If at any time you would like to opt out of receiving such promotions please email [opt-out@brainmass.com](mailto:opt-out@brainmass.com). BM may also provide to third parties aggregate or statistical information that does not disclose personally identifiable information.

BM may display targeted advertisements of interest or benefit to you based on nonpublic personal information. If you respond to these advertisements and then give the advertiser personal information about yourself, you may reveal to the advertiser or ad server that you possess the characteristics used to select the audience for the advertisement.

  * BM does not share any personally identifiable information about you with any third parties when you click on these ads.
  * BM advertisers may include financial service providers (such as mortgage bankers, securities broker-dealers, and insurance agents) and non-financial companies (such as retailers, airlines, and publishers).

If you do not wish to disclose information about yourself to advertisers, you may choose to communicate with the advertiser directly in a manner that does not disclose that you viewed the BM advertisement.

Except for the above parties, and for use by BM's consultants and professional advisers on BM's behalf for the uses disclosed herein, BM does not share personal information with any other third parties. BM may, however, provide to third parties aggregate or statistical information that does not disclose personally identifiable information.

BM may display targeted advertisements of interest or benefit to you based on nonpublic personal information. If you respond to these advertisements and then give the advertiser personal information about yourself, you may reveal to the advertiser or ad server that you possess the characteristics used to select the audience for the advertisement.

  * BM does not share any personally identifiable information about you with any third parties when you click on these ads.
  * BM advertisers may include financial service providers (such as mortgage bankers, securities broker-dealers, and insurance agents) and non-financial companies (such as retailers, airlines, and publishers).

If you do not wish to disclose information about yourself to advertisers, you may choose to communicate with the advertiser directly in a manner that does not disclose that you viewed the BM advertisement.

**Confidentiality and Security**

We restrict access to your nonpublic personal information to those employees who reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.

Contact Us / Email Inquiries:

No information sent to BrainMass.com via email or the website inquiry form is used for any other reason than to respond to and maintain a record of the inquiry. This information is not sent to third parties or retained for mailing list purposes.

**Corrections / Update**

This site gives Online Teaching Assistants and student-users the following options for removing their information from our database to cancel future communications, to no longer receive our service, or to change their information on our database:

  1. Send email to [contact@brainmass.com](mailto:contact@brainmass.com) (Online Teaching Assistants).
  2. Send email to [operations@brainmass.com](mailto:operations@brainmass.com) (Student-users).

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

BM may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

**Contacting BM**

If you have questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this web site, you may contact:

BrainMass.com  
76 Prospect Street  
Newmarket, ON, Canada  
L3Y 3T2  
Email: [contact@brainmass.com](mailto:contact@brainmass.com)

© BrainMass Inc. 2010  
Last updated September 1, 2010
